purplle.com 2017-06-06

# privacy policy|Buy Hair products,Cosmetics,Perfumes online|Purplle.com

The domain name www.purplle.com (hereinafter referred to as "Website") is owned by Manash Lifestyle Private Limited a company incorporated under the Companies Act, 1956 with its registered office at 204, Jhalawar ,Patanwala EST, LBS MArg , Ghatkopar (W), Mumbai – 400086 (hereinafter referred to as "Manash").

**Purplle Privacy Policy**  
We value the trust you place in Manash. That's why we insist upon the highest standards for secure transactions and customer information privacy. Please read the following statement to learn about our information gathering and dissemination practices. Note: Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without notice. To make sure you are aware of any changes, please review this policy periodically. 

**Collection of Personally Identifiable Information**  
We collect personally identifiable information (email address, name,phone number, etc.) from you when you set up a free account with the Website. While you can browse some sections of our site without being a registered member, certain activities (such as placing an order) do require registration. We do use your contact information to send you offers based on your previous orders and your interests. 

**Use of Demographic and Profile Data**  
We use personal information to provide the services you request. To the extent we use your personal information to market to you, we will provide you the ability to opt-out of such uses. We use your personal information to resolve disputes; troubleshoot problems; help promote a safe service; collect fees owed; measure consumer interest in our products and services, inform you about online and offline offers, products, services, and updates; customize your experience; detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity; enforce our terms and conditions; and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection. 

In our efforts to continually improve our product and service offerings, we collect and analyze demographic and profile data about our users' activity on our website.We identify and use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information. 

We will occasionally ask you to complete optional online surveys. These surveys may ask you for contact information and demographic information (like zip code, age, or income level). We use this data to tailor your experience at our site, providing you with content that we think you might be interested in--and to display content according to your preferences. 

**Cookies**  
A "cookie" is a small piece of information stored by a Web server on a Web browser so it can be later read back from that browser. Cookies are useful for enabling the browser to remember information specific to a given user. the Website places both permanent and temporary cookies in your computer's hard drive. Website’s cookies do not contain any of your personally identifiable information. 

**Retention and Usage of Sensitive Personal Data or Information**  
Except as reasonably required or otherwise permitted or required by applicable law or regulatory requirements, Manash endeavours to retain your Sensitive Personal Data or Information only for as long as it believes is necessary to fulfill the purposes for which the Sensitive Personal Data or Information was collected (including, for the purpose of meeting any legal, administrative, accounting, regulatory or other reporting requirements or obligations). This Sensitive Personal Data or Information is safeguarded against inappropriate access and disclosure, as per this Privacy Policy. 

**Sharing of personal information**  
We may share personal information with our other corporate entities and affiliates to: help detect and prevent identity theft, fraud and other potentially illegal acts; correlate related or multiple accounts to prevent abuse of our services; and to facilitate joint or co-branded services that you request where such services are provided by more than one corporate entity. Those entities and affiliates may not market to you as a result of such sharing unless you explicitly opt-in. 

We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process. We may disclose personal information to law enforcement offices, third party rights owners, or others in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to: enforce our Terms or Privacy Policy; respond to claims that an advertisement, posting or other content violates the rights of a third party; or protect the rights, property or personal safety of our users or the general public. Manash and its affiliates will share some or all of your personal information with another business entity should we (or our assets) plan to merge with, or be acquired by that business entity. Should such a transaction occur, that other business entity (or the new combined entity) will be required to follow this privacy policy with respect to your personal information. 

**Links to Other Sites**  
Our site links to other websites that may collect personally identifiable information about you. Manash is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those linked websites. 

**Information Security Practices and Procedures**  
Manash endeavors to maintain physical, technical and procedural safeguards that are appropriate to protect your Personal Information including Sensitive Personal Data or Information against loss, misuse, copying, damage or modification and unauthorized access or disclosure Our site has stringent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Whenever you change or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. Once your information is in our possession we adhere to strict security guidelines, protecting it against unauthorized access. 

**Choice/Opt-Out**  
The Website provides all users with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving non-essential (promotional, marketing-related) communications from us on behalf of our partners, and from us in general, after setting up an account. If you want to remove your contact information from all Purplle.com lists and newsletters, please visit http://purplle.com/unsubscribe.php 

**Disclaimer**

The information contained in this website is for general information purposes only. The information is provided by Purplle.com and while we endeavour to keep the information up to date and correct, we make no representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, about the completeness, accuracy, reliability, suitability or availability with respect to the website or the information, products, services, or related graphics contained on the website for any purpose. Any reliance you place on such information is therefore strictly at your own risk.

In no event will we be liable for any loss or damage including without limitation, indirect or consequential loss or damage, or any loss or damage whatsoever arising from loss of data or profits arising out of, or in connection with, the use of this website.

Through this website you are able to link to other websites which are not under the control of. We have no control over the nature, content and availability of those sites. The inclusion of any links does not necessarily imply a recommendation or endorse the views expressed within them.

Every effort is made to keep the website up and running smoothly. However, Purplle.com takes no responsibility for, and will not be liable for, the website being temporarily unavailable due to technical issues beyond our control.
